A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.25 (A99) FA477
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A99), 1974-1999; 1.25; 99.6 Cubic Feet; 83 standard record storage cartons. Boxes R3191-R3252, R3266-R3286.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF)
    - RF 92109 - JOINT CENTER FOR POLITICAL STUDIES - PUBLIC POLICY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, Multiple folders. (Box R3218)
    - RF 92109 - JOINT CENTER FOR POLITICAL STUDIES - PUBLIC POLICY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, Multiple folders. (Box R3219)
    - RF 92109 - JOINT CENTER FOR POLITICAL STUDIES - PUBLIC POLICY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, Multiple folders. (Box R3220)
    - RF 92109 - JOINT CENTER FOR POLITICAL STUDIES - PUBLIC POLICY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, Multiple folders. (Box R3221)
    - RF 92116 - URBAN INSTITUTE - PERSISTENT URBAN POVERTY, 1987-1997; 3 folders. (Box R3222)
    - RF 92116 - URBAN INSTITUTE - PERSISTENT URBAN POVERTY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 3 folders. (Box R3223)
    - RF 93001 A 175 - UTAH STATE UNIVERSITY (HOAR) - CHARACTERIZATION OF A NEW APOMICTIC RICE LINE, 1991-1994, 1997 (Box R3223)
    - RF 93001 A 189 - UNIVERSITY OF GEORGIA - IDENTIFICATION AND CHARACTERIZATION OF ENDOPHYTES IN RICE, 1993-1997 (Box R3223)
    - RF 93001 A 192 - WASHINGTON STATE UNIVERSITY - RICE MALE STERILITY, 1990-1996 (Box R3223)
    - RF 93003 A 168 - AGRICULTURAL BIOTECHNOLOGY INSTITUTE, RURAL DEVELOPMENT ADMINISTRATION (KOREA) - RESEARCH ON TRANSGENIC RICE PLANTS IN INDICA RICE, 1993-1997 (Box R3223)
    - RF 93003 A 169 - PUNJAB AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - TRANSGENIC PLANTS IN INDICA RICE, 1993-1997 (Box R3223)
    - RF 93003 A 183 - CENTRAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE FOR FOOD CROPS (INDONESIA) - QTL'S AFFECTING AGRONOMIC TRAITS OF JAVANICA RICE, 1992-1997 (Box R3223)
    - RF 93003 A 184 - FUDAN UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY/GENOME MAPPING FELLOWSHIP, 1992-1997 (Box R3223)
    - RF 93003 A 207 - SCRIPPS RESEARCH INSTITUTE - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR JIANMIN WANG, 1993-1997 (Box R3224)
    - RF 93003 A 214 - ZHEJIANG AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY FELLOWSHIP, 1993-1997 (Box R3224)
    - RF 93005 A 12 - CARTER, SIMON EDWARD - RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP IN AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES, 1991-1996 (Box R3224)
    - RF 93005 A 13 - MONTEITH, STEVEN E. - RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP IN AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES IN AGRONOMY, 1994-1995, 1998 (Box R3224)
    - RF 93010 A 26 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - LEAD PROGRAM'S INTERNATIONAL SESSION IN COSTA RICA, 1993-1994, 1997-1998 (Box R3224)
    - RF 93010 A 34 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - LEAD PROGRAM'S INTERNATIONAL STEERING COMMITTEE MEETING IN JAMAICA, 1993, 1998 (Box R3224)
    - RF 93012 A 3 - WORLD ASSOCIATION OF COMMUNITY RADIO BROADCASTERS (CANADA) - AMARC SIXTH WORLD CONFERENCE, 1995-1996 (Box R3224)
    - RF 93012 A 4 - INSTITUTE FOR DEMOCRACY IN SOUTH AFRICA RADIO SERIES PRESENTING ORAL HISTORIES, 1994-1995 (Box R3224)
    - RF 93013 A 525 - COLEGIO DE LA FRONTERA NORTE - CULTURAL IDENTITIES OF THE MEXICAN POPULATION, 1991-1993, 1998 (Box R3224)
    - RF 93013 A 529 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (LOS ANGELES) - SYMPOSIUM ON ASIAN-AMERICAN DIALOGUE IN ARTS AND HUMANITIES, 1993-1995, 1998-1999 (Box R3224)
      Records more than 20 years old are open for scholarly research, with prior archival review. Entire file open in 2020. Retrieval time may exceed 24 hours.
    - RF 93014 A 81 - NEW MUSEUM OF CONTEMPORARY ART ? "TRADE ROUTES" EXHIBITION, 1991-1994 (Box R3224)
    - RF 93014 A 83 - MUSEUM OF FINE ARTS, HOUSTON - ART OF JOHN BIGGERS, 1993-1995 (Box R3224)
    - RF 93014 A 84 - MUSEUM OF NEW MEXICO FOUNDATION - MUSEUM OF INTERNATIONAL FOLK ART'S EXHIBITION "RECYCLED, RESEEN: FOLK ART IN A POST-INDUSTRIAL WORLD", 1991-1996 (Box R3225)
    - RF 93014 A 88 - CENTER FOR AFRICAN ART- AFRICAN PARTICIPATION IN 1993 VENICE BIENNALE, 1992-1996 (Box R3225)
    - 930018-7 - INTERNATIONAL AFRICAN INSTITUTE (ENGLAND) - WORKSHOP, "MUSEUMS AND HISTORY", RELATED ACTIVITIES, 1993-1995 (Box R3225)
    - RF 93019 A 119 - LOS ANGELES EDUCATIONAL PARTNERSHIP - ARTS AND HUMANITIES TEACHERS, 1984-1996; 4 folders. (Box R3225)
    - RF 93019 A 119 - LOS ANGELES EDUCATIONAL PARTNERSHIP - ARTS AND HUMANITIES TEACHERS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 3 folders. (Box R3226)
    - 930019-122 - ALLIANCE FOR CURRICULUM REFORM - RESEARCH SYNTHESIS FOR IMPROVING STUDENT ACHIEVEMENTS, 1994-1996 (Box R3226)
    - 930019-123 - INTERNATIONAL EDUCATION CONSORTIUM - COORDINATION OF THE CHART NETWORK, 1994-1995 (Box R3226)
    - RF 93019 A 131 - LOS ANGELES EDUCATIONAL PARTNERSHIP - HUMANITAS TEACHER'S FACULTY RETREATS, 1995 (Box R3226)
    - RF 93021 - WASHINGTON CENTER FOR CHINA STUDIES INC.- ENABLE U.S.-BASED CHINESE SCHOLARS 1993-96 TO USE SHORT-TERM FELLOWSHIPS IN CHINA, 1993-1996 (Box R3226)
    - RF 93023 A 28 - CENTRE FOR LAND AND BIOLOGICAL RESEARCH (CANADA) - CASE STUDIES IN SUSTAINABLE LAND MANAGEMENT WITHIN RF'S PROGRAM IN MEXICO, 1994-1997 (Box R3227)
    - RF 93025 - NATIONAL POLYTECHNIC INSTITUTE (MEXICO CITY) - PROPRIETARY BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1990-1998 (Box R3227)
    - RF 93026 - CASSAVA BIOTECHNOLOGY RESEARCH NETWORK, 1988-1993 (Box R3227)
    - RF 93027 A 400 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - PHARMACOEPIDEMIOLOGY PROJECT, 1992-1996 (Box R3227)
    - RF 93027 A 401 - UNIVERSITY OF THE PHILIPPINES - "PREMATURE RUPTURE OF MEMBRANES AND RISK OF NEONATAL SEPSIS", 1992-1993 (Box R3227)
    - RF 93027 A 402 - UNIVERSIDAD DE LA FRONTERA (CHILE) - DEVELOPMENT OF SURVEY INSTRUMENT FOR DETECTING ALCOHOL ABUSE, 1992-1993 (Box R3227)
    - RF 93027 A 403 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - PRETERM LABOUR AND MATERNAL INFECTIONS, 1992-1993 (Box R3227)
    - RF 93027 A 404 - UNIVERSIDAD DE LA FRONTERA (CHILE) - APPROACHES IN DEVELOPMENT OF CHILD ABUSE, 1993 (Box R3227)
    - RF 93027 A 405 - GADJAH MADA UNIVERSITY (INDONESIA) - PROJECT IN BIOSTATISTICS "MASTER OF MEDICAL STATISTICS", 1992-1993 (Box R3227)
    - RF 93027 A 406 - SUEZ CANAL UNIVERSITY (EGYPT) - IMMUNIZATION OF NEWBORN AGAINST HEPATITIS B VIRUS INFECTION, 1992-1994 (Box R3227)
    - RF 93028 A 12 - UGANDAN NURSE-MIDWIVE TRAINING, 1989-1997; 2 folders. (Box R3227)
    - RF 93031 A 348 - KISIARA, RICHARD - ADIA: LABOR EXCHANGE IN POLYETHNIC AGRICULTURAL RESETTLEMENT IN KENYA, 1993-1997 (Box R3228)
    - RF 93013 A 350 - KALIF, ABDULLAH I - ADIA: POLYMERASE CHAIN REACTION RESEARCH, 1993-1997 (Box R3228)
    - RF 93031 A 373 - WOELK, GODFREY BENJAMIN - ADIA: BIRTH WEIGHT AND BLOOD PRESSURE/CHILDREN AND PARENTS, 1993-1997 (Box R3228)
    - RF 93031 A 378 - OWUSU-ANSAH, JOSEPH - ADIA: EXTENSION PROJECTS AND POLICY, 1992-1997 (Box R3228)
    - RF 93031 A 392 - GEBISSA, EZEKIAL - ADIA: "FROM COFFEE TO CHAT", 1993-1997 (Box R3228)
    - RF 93031 A 394 - AM BALl, AGGREY - ADIA: TILAPIAS IN MALAWI, 1993-1997 (Box R3228)
    - RF 93031 A 396 - MPOFU, BELLAH- ADIA: "INTEGRATED CONTROL OF EICHHORNIA CRASSIPES {MART.) SOLMS (PONTEDERIACEAE) IN ZIMBABWE", 1992-1997 (Box R3228)
    - RF 93031 A 399 - NGALAMULUME, KALALA - ADIA: HEALTH CARE IN SENEGAL, 1850-1950, 1993-1998 (Box R3228)
    - RF 93031 A 404 - ABDELKADIR, ABDU - ADIA: EFFECT OF TREE DENSITY IN ALLEY CROPPING SYSTEMS, 1993-1997 (Box R3228)
    - RF 93031 A 413 - TARHULE, AUGUSTINE - ADIA: ANALYSIS OF DROUGHTS, 1993-1997 (Box R3228)
    - RF 93031 A 415 - DUANY, AKER JULIA- ADIA: SUDANESE WOMEN AND EDUCATION, 1993-1997 (Box R3228)
    - RF 93034 A 18 - MICHIGAN STATE UNIVERSITY- DISSEMINATION OF ARTICLE ON RF-SPONSORED SCHOOL, DISTRICT AND STATE LEADERSHIP ACADEMIES, 1993-1997 (Box R3228)
    - RF 93034 A 18 - MICHIGAN STATE UNIVERSITY- DISSEMINATION OF ARTICLE ON RF-SPONSORED SCHOOL, DISTRICT AND STATE LEADERSHIP ACADEMIES - SUPPLEMENTARY MAATERIAL, 1993-1997; 2 folders. (Box R3228)
    - RF 93038 A 24 - AFRICAN WILDLIFE FOUNDATION - LAND USE CHANGE IN WILDLIFE DISPERSAL AREAS OF AMBOSELI ECOSYSTEMS (KENYA), 1991-1997 (Box R3228)
    - 930038-37 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR RESEARCH IN AGROFORESTRY (KENYA)- IMPROVED MANAGEMENT IN EASTERN AFRICA, 1992-1997 (Box R3229)
    - 930038-38 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (IITA) (NIGERIA) - WORKSHOP ACTIVITIES OF ITS SOIL AND PLANT ANALYTICAL LABORATORY NETWORK FOR AFRICA (SPALNA), 1994-1996 (Box R3229)
    - RF 9039 A 74 - SNYDER, KATHERINE ANN - SSRF: ECONOMIC OR SOCIAL ASPECTS OF AGROFORESTRY TECHNOLOGIES, 1992-1997 (Box R3229)
    - RF 93040 A 21 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - TERMITE CONTROL IN SMALLHOLDER MAIZE-BASED FARMING SYSTEMS, 1993-1994, 1997 (Box R3229)
    - 930040-29 - WYE COLLEGE - UNIVERSITY OF LONDON - (ENGLAND) - DISTANCE LEARNING COURSE FOR AGRONOMISTS, 1994, 1997 (Box R3229)
    - 930040-30 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - ECOLOGICAL RELATIONSHIPS BETWEEN SOIL NEMATODES AS BIO-INDICATORS OF SUSTAINABLE LAND USE IN SOUTHERN AFRICA, 1994, 1997 (Box R3229)
    - RF 93048 A 4 - UNIVERSITY OF ARIZONA - STAGED READING OF THE SHADOW BOX, 1993-1995 (Box R3229)
    - RF 93049 A 1 - WOMEN LIVING UNDER MUSLIM LAWS (FRANCE) - SUPPORT DOCUMENTATION CENTER, 1993-1996 (Box R3229)
    - RF 93049 A 1 - WOMEN LIVING UNDER MUSLIM LAWS (FRANCE) - SUPPORT DOCUMENTATION CENTER - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 2 folders. (Box R3229)
    - 930049-3 - SANART 92, ASSOCIATION FOR THE PROMOTION OF VISUAL ARTS IN TURKEY - MUSEUMS IN CONTEMPORARY TURKISH SOCIETY, 1994-1996 (Box R3229)
    - 930049-4 - TURKISH ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL HISTORY FOUNDATION (TURKEY) - EXHIBIT ON IMMIGRATION, ETHNICITY AND PLURALISM ú ESTABLISH TURKISH SOCIAL HISTORY MUSEUM, 1993-1996 (Box R3229)
    - 930049-4 - TURKISH ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL HISTORY FOUNDATION (TURKEY) - EXHIBIT ON IMMIGRATION, ETHNICITY AND PLURALISM ú ESTABLISH TURKISH SOCIAL HISTORY MUSEUM - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R3229)
    - RF 93050 A 132 - VIDEAZIMUT (CANADA) - 1994 INTERNATIONAL SYMPOSIUM ON NEW TECHNOLOGIES AND DEMOCRATIC COMMUNICATIONS, 1993-1995 (Box R3230)
    - 930050-145 - FOUNDATION FOR ART IN CINEMA - EXHIBIT AND WIDEN IMPACT OF EXPERIMENTAL FILM AND VIDEO, 1993-1996 (Box R3230)
    - 930050-147 - REDROAD, RANDY - "HIGH HORSE", 1994-1996 (Box R3230)
    - 930050-148 - VALADEZ, JOHN - "MEMORY AGAINST FORGETTING", 1994-1996 (Box R3230)
    - 930050-149 - DWOSKIN, STEPHEN -"IN A STRANGE LAND WITHIN MY OWN COUNTRY", 1993-1996 (Box R3230)
    - 930050-150 - DONG, ARTHUR - "THEY CALLED US LESBIANS", 1994-1997 (Box R3230)
    - 930050-152 - DE MICHIEL, HELEN - FILM, "TARANTELLA", 1994-1995 (Box R3230)
    - 930050-154 - WILLIAMS, DAVID D. - FILM, "THIRTEEN", 1994-1995 (Box R3230)
    - 930050-155 - DING, LONI - "CHINESE LAUNDRYMAN'S CHILDREN", 1994, 1997 (Box R3230)
    - 930050-157 - TAJIMA, RENEE- ROAD TRILOGY: FORTUNE COOKIES; THE SEARCH FOR ASIAN AMERICA LA REUNION, 1994-1996 (Box R3230)
    - 930050-156 - ZAGDANSKY, ANDREI - "FRAGMENTS OF A CORRESPONDENCE WITH MY FATHER", 1993-1995 (Box R3230)
    - 930050-158 - JONES, PHILLIP MALLORY - "FIRST WORLD ORDER INSTALLATION PROJECT", 1994-1996 (Box R3230)
    - 930050-159 - OSORIO, PEPON - "EN LA BARBERIA NO SE LLORA", 1993-1996 (Box R3230)
    - 930050-160 - SMITH, CAULEEN - "INDIGO TRILOGY", 1994-1996 (Box R3230)
    - 930050-162 - BRITISH FILM INSTITUTE (UNITED KINGDOM) - SUB-SAHARAN PROGRAM IN TV SERIES, 100 YEARS OF CINEMA, 1994-1996 (Box R3230)
    - 930050-165 - FILM RESOURCE UNIT (SOUTH AFRICA) - DISTRIBUTION PROGRAMME FOR INDEPENDENT EDUCATIONAL FILM, 1994-1996 (Box R3230)
    - 930050-166 - SYGNIFYN' WORKS - "BLACK IS...BLACK AIN'T", 1994 (Box R3230)
    - 930050-167 - INTERNATIONAL FILM SEMINARS, INC. - 1994 ROBERT FLAHERTY INTERNATIONAL FILM SEMINARS, 1994-1995 (Box R3231)
    - RF 93050 A 170 - SUNDANCE INSTITUTE FOR FILM AND TELEVISION - NEW MEDIA INITIATIVE, 1994, 1997 (Box R3231)
    - RF 93050 A 171 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (LOS ANGELES) - BC CONFERENCE: CURATORS ACROSS CULTURES, 1994-1997 (Box R3231)
    - RF 93053 A 129 - ARTS COMPANY, INC. - WOMEN IN MY LIFE, 1993-1997 (Box R3231)
    - RF 93053 A 136 - OTROVENA SCENA OBALA (OPEN STATE OBALA) (BOSNIA/HERZEGOVINA) - "WITNESS OF EXISTENCE", 1993-1995 (Box R3231)
    - RF 93053 A 153 - DELL'ARTE, INC.- CREATION PROJECT, 1993-1994, 1997 (Box R3231)
    - RF 93053 A 155 - BREAD AND PUPPET THEATRE- U.S. - NICARAGUAN PUPPETRY PROJECT, 1993-1994, 1997 (Box R3231)
    - RF 93053 A 156 - LOS ANGELES POVERTY DEPARTMENT - COLLABORATION WITH LOCAL ARTISTS, 1993-1995 (Box R3231)
    - RF 93053 A 158 - SANTA FE SYMPHONY ORCHESTRA AND CHORUS, INC. - NEW WORK: FULL SYMPHONY, 1993-1995 (Box R3231)
    - RF 93053 A 159 - GAMELAN PACIFICA - COLUMBIAN EXPOSITION CENTENNIAL PROJECT, 1993, 1997 (Box R3231)
    - RF 93053 A 162 - ALLENTOWN FESTIVAL ASSOCIATION INC. (AKA MAYFAIR) - BILINGUAL THEATER WORK, 1993-1995 (Box R3231)
    - RF 93053 A 169 - ANCHORAGE CIVIC OPERA ASSOCIATION, INC. - "EARTH AND THE GREAT WEATHER", 1993-1997 (Box R3231)
    - 930053-170 - REPERTORIO ESPANOL- "A LA DIESTRA DE DIOS PADRE", 1993-1997 (Box R3231)
    - RF 93053 A 172 - HOUSE FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - SONG OF THE LARK, 1994-1997 (Box R3231)
    - RF 93053 A 173 - CORNERSTONE THEATER CO. - SAN MIGUEL PROJECT, 1994-1997 (Box R3231)
    - RF 93053 A 174 - CENTER FOR THE ARTS AT VERBA BUENA GARDENS - YOUTH PERFORMING ARTS FESTIVAL, 1994-1997 (Box R3231)
    - RF 93053 A 175 - DANCE THEATER WORKSHOP - A BLACK BURLESQUE, 1994-1996 (Box R3231)
    - RF 93053 A 176 - GROUP (THE)- UNDESIRABLE ELEMENTS/SEATTLE, 1994-1997 (Box R3231)
    - RF 93053 A 177 - WASHINGTON PERFORMING ARTS SOCIETY - THE DANGEROUS BORDER GAME, 1994-1996 (Box R3232)
    - RF 93053 A 178 - 18TH STREET ARTS COMPLEX - THE DODO VACCINE, 1994-1997 (Box R3232)
    - RF 93053 A 181 - CULTURAL ODYSSEY- STREET WARS: STAYING ALIVE, 1994, 1997 (Box R3232)
    - RF 93053 A 184 - FOUNDATION FOR INDEPENDENT ARTISTS - RIVER, 1994, 1997 (Box R3232)
    - RF 93053 A 185 - FOUNDATION FOR INDEPENDENT ARTISTS - WINGS OF FAITH, 1994, 1997 (Box R3232)
    - RF 93054 A 14 - CENTRO CULTURAL CIUDAD DE BUENOS AIRES - COMPUTER MUSIC RESIDENCY EXCHANGE PROGRAM, 1987-1996 (Box R3232)
    - RF 93055 A 62 - PITON FOUNDATION - PERSISTENT POVERTY PROJECTS, 1991-1996; 2 folders. (Box R3232)
    - RF 93055 A 62 - PITON FOUNDATION - PERSISTENT POVERTY PROJECTS, 1986-1990; 3 folders. (Box R3233)
    - RF 93055 A 62 - PITON FOUNDATION - PERSISTENT POVERTY PROJECTS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIALS, 2 folders. (Box R3233)
    - RF 93055 A 62 - PITON FOUNDATION - PERSISTENT POVERTY PROJECTS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIALS (Box R3234)
    - RF 93055 A 65 - GREATER WASHINGTON RESEARCH CENTER CENSUS DATA & INCOME TAX CREDIT CAMPAIGNS, 1986-1995; 5 folders. (Box R3234)
    - RF 93055 A 65 - GREATER WASHINGTON RESEARCH CENTER CENSUS DATA & INCOME TAX CREDIT CAMPAIGNS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 3 folders. (Box R3235)
    - RF 93056 A 4 - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH COUNCIL - BC CONFERENCE: SOCIAL SUFFERING: EXPERIENCE, REPRESENTATION, POLICY, 1993-1994 (Box R3235)
    - 930056-6 - LEVINSON, F. JAMES - BC CONFERENCE: ADDRESSING NUTRITION MALPRACTICE, 1993-1995 (Box R3235)
    - 930063-76 - CENTER FOR RESEARCH IN HUMAN REPRODUCTION (PANAMA) - CRYOPRESERVATION OF HUMAN SPERMATOZOA, 1994 (Box R3235)
    - RF 93065 A 48 - THIRD WORLD ORGANIZATION FOR WOMEN IN SCIENCE (ITALY) - PARTICIAPATION OF GIRLS IN STUDY OF SCIENCE IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 1993-1995 (Box R3235)
    - 930065-50 - KIFLEYESUS, ABEBE - ARGOBBA WOMEN TRADERS' ACCESS TO FORMAL EDUCATION, 1992-1996 (Box R3235)
    - 930066-34 - UNIVERSITY OF DAR ES SALAAM - SCIENCE CAMP, 1987-1996, 1999; 2 folders. (Box R3236)
    - RF 93066 A 44 - AFRICAN FORUM ON CHILDREN'S TECHNOLOGICAL LITERACY - PRINT PRODUCTION WORKSHOP, 1994-1995 (Box R3236)
    - RF 93067 A 6 - DEARBORN INSTITUTE FOR CONFLICT RESOLUTION - MANAGEMENT OF MEDICAL WASTE IN ILLINOIS, 1995-1996 (Box R3236)
    - RF 93067 A 13 - FLORENCE R. CLUCKHOHN CENTER - "WHATCOM COUNTY PARTNERSHIP PROJECT", 1995-1996 (Box R3236)
    - RF 93069 - NATIONAL ASSOCIATION FOR THE ADVANCEMENT OF COLORED PEOPLE - (SPECIAL CONTRIBUTION FUND) - EMPLOYMENT DISCRIMINATION, 1986-1995; 3 folders. (Box R3236)
    - 940001-281 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION SEVENTH ANNUAL MEETING OF THE INTERNATIONAL PROGRAM ON RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1993-1996 (Box R3237)
    - 940001-291 - BIOTECHNOLOGY RESEARCH CENTER (VIETNAM) - TRAINING IN RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY FOR NGUYEN HUU HO, 1994-1996 (Box R3237)
    - 940001-296 - PUNJAB AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - TRAINING IN RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY FOR VI RASH KAMAL GUPTA, 1994-1996 (Box R3237)
    - RF 94001 A 299 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - GENETICS OF HYBRID RICE, 1990-1997 (Box R3237)
    - RF 94001 A 302 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - IMPROVEMENT OF RICE GRAIN QUALITY, 1994-1996 (Box R3237)
    - 940006-8 - INTERNATIONAL UNION FOR THE SCIENTIFIC STUDY OF POPULATION (BELGIUM) - SEMINAR ON DEMOGRAPHY AND POVERTY, 1993-1996 (Box R3237)
    - RF 94006 A 23 - FAMILY CARE INTERNATIONAL - CONCENSUS BUILDING FOR THE ICPD AND BEYOND, 1993-1995 (Box R3237)
    - RF 94006 A 31 - WOMEN U.S.A. FUND - IMPLEMENTATION OF CAIRO PROGRAMME OF ACTION AT INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCES, 1995-1996 (Box R3237)
    - RF 94006 A 32 - WESTERN CONSORTIUM FOR PUBLIC HEALTH - INTERNATIONAL WOMEN'S DAY; WOMEN'S CONFERENCE IN BEIJING, 1995-1999 (Box R3237)
    - RF 94008 A 45 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - LEAD PROGRAM'S INTERNATIONAL SESSION IN ZIMBABWE, 1993-1998 (Box R3237)
    - 940008-47 - ROYAL SWEDISH ACADEMY OF SCIENCES (SWEDEN) - DISTRIBUTION OF AMBIO AND PUBLICATION OF ARTICLES ON LEAD, 1994-1996 (Box R3237)
    - 940008-56 - PEKING UNIVERSITY- LEAD NATIONAL PROGRAM IN CHINA, 1993-1995, 1999 (Box R3237)
    - RF 94010 A 545 - INSTITUTE OF ADVANCED STUDY - CONFERENCE ON WOMEN AND FEMINISM IN COUNTRIES UNDERGOING POLITICAL AND ECONOMIC TRANSITION, 1994-1997 (Box R3237)
    - RF 94010 A 546 - CULTURAL ASSOCIATION FOR CONTEMPORARY STUDIES (BRAZIL) - "CULTURE TROUBLE": SECOND CONFERENCE OF INTER-AMERICAN CULTURAL STUDIES NETWORK, 1994-1995 (Box R3237)
    - RF 94011 A 5 - WATUTU FOUNDATION - KENYAN PARTICIPATION IN 1995 JOHANNESBURG INTERNATIONAL BIENNALE, 1994, 1999 (Box R3237)
    - RF 94011 A 8 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - BC CONFERENCE: DONORS INTERESTED IN AFRICAN CULTURAL DEVELOPMENT, 1994-1997 (Box R3237)
    - 94012-93 - CALIFORNIA AFRO-AMERICAN MUSEUM FOUNDATION - EXHIBITION, "JOHN OUTTERBRIDGE: A RETROSPECTIVE", 1994-1996 (Box R3238)
    - 940012-94 - EXIT ART, INC. - 1994 EXHIBITIONS PROGRAM, 1992-1996 (Box R3238)
    - 940012-96 - SEEM FOUNDATION FOR THE ADVANCEMENT OF MUSIC- EXHIBITION, "THE MUSICAL RENAISSANCE OF BLACK LOS ANGELES", 1994-1996 (Box R3238)
    - 940012-97 - ARIZONA STATE UNIVERSITY FOUNDATION - EXHIBITION, "ART UNDER DURESS: EL SALVADOR 1980-PRESENT", 1993-1997 (Box R3238)
    - 940012-98 - FOOTHILL-DE ANZA COMMUNITY COLLEGE DISTRICT- EXHIBITION, "COMING ACROSS: ART BY RECENT IMMIGRANTS, PART 2", 1994-1995 (Box R3238)
    - 940012-99 - WHITNEY MUSEUM OF AMERICAN ART - EXHIBITION, "BLACK MALE...", 1994-1995 (Box R3238)
    - 940012-100 - ANCHORAGE FINE ARTS MUSEUM ASSOCIATION -EXHIBITION, "EMBRACING THE SPIRIT: THE LIVING TRADITION OF YUP'IK MASKS", 1993-1997 (Box R3238)
    - 940012-102 - NEWARK MUSEUM ASSOCIATION- EXHIBITION OF WORKS BY PEPON OSORIO, 1994-1996 (Box R3238)
    - 940012-103 - UNIVERSITY OF ARIZONA- EXHIBITION: "RECONSTRUCTION: WILLIAM CHRISTENBERRY'S ART", 1994-1996 (Box R3238)
    - 940012-106 - IOG FILMS - NAGASAKI JOURNEY EXHIBITION, 1993-1995 (Box R3238)
    - RF 94012 A 108 - MINT MUSEUM OF ART- EXHIBITION MICHAEL LUCERO: SCULPTURE 1976-1994, 1994-1997 (Box R3239)
    - RF 94012 A 109 - STOREFRONT FOR ART AND ARCHITECTURE EXHIBITION: "HOUSING FOR THE 21ST CENTURY: ECOLOGY OF HOME", 1993-1997 (Box R3239)
    - RF 94012 A 111 - NEW JERSEY HISTORICAL SOCIETY - EXHIBITION, "CARIBBEAN FOLK ARTS IN NEW JERSEY", 1994, 1997 (Box R3239)
    - RF 94014 A 118 - ALTERNATE ROOTS - NEW WORKS COMMISSIONING PROGRAM, 1993-1997 (Box R3239)
    - RF 94014 A 120 - DIVERSE WORKS, INC. - INTERDISCIPLINARY ARTISTS, 1985-1997 (Box R3239)
    - RF 94014 A 121 - HELENA FILM SOCIETY, INC. - INTERDISCIPLINARY ARTISTS, 1989-1997 (Box R3239)
    - RF 94014 A 122 - INTERMEDIA ARTS MINNESOTA INTERDISCIPLINARY ARTISTS, 1986-1995 (Box R3239)
    - RF 94014 A 124 - NEW ENGLAND FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS ? INTERDISCIPLINARY ARTISTS, 1989-1997 (Box R3239)
    - RF 94015 A 74 - INSTITUTE OF INTERNATIONAL EDUCATION - BC CONFERENCE: GROUNDS FOR DIFFERENCE: CROSS-EXAMINATION OF THE INTERNATIONAL FESTIVAL GENRE, 1995-1997 (Box R3240)
    - RF 94017 A 7 - SAN FRANCISCO UNIFIED SCHOOL DISTRICT - BUILDING AN INFRASTRUCTURE FOR PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT, 1994-1996 (Box R3240)
    - RF 94014 A 127 - PAINTED BRIDE ART CENTER - INTERDISCIPLINARY ARTISTS, 1985-1997; 2 folders. (Box R3240)
    - RF 94014 A 128 - RANDOLPH STREET GALLERY - INTERDISCIPLINARY ARTISTS, 1988-1997; 2 folders. (Box R3240)
    - 940015-64 - HENSON FOUNDATION - PRODUCTION OF "WOYZECK IN JOHANNESBURG", 1993-1995 (Box R3240)
    - 940015-70 - PEPATIAN, INC. - ROMPEFORMA FIFTH ANNUAL FESTIVAL, 1994-1995 (Box R3240)
    - 940015-71 - VISUAL ARTS RESOURCES AND RESEARCH CENTER RELATING TO THE CARIBBEAN - EXPRESSIONS INTERNATIONAL FESTIVAL ON NEW WORLD AFRICANS, 1993-1995 (Box R3240)
    - RF 94015 A 72 - SONORAN INSTITUTE - "CELEBRATION OF DESERT CULTURES" FESTIVAL, 1994-1997 (Box R3240)
    - RF 94015 A 73 - PHILIPPINE INFORMATION EDUCATION AND RESOURCE CENTER - SECOND FILIPINO AMERICAN ARTS EXPOSITION, 1994-1997 (Box R3240)
    - RF 94017 A 8 - DENVER PUBLIC SCHOOLS - BUILDING AN INFRASTRUCTURE FOR PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT, 1994-1996 (Box R3241)
    - RF 94017 A 8 - PITTSBURGH PUBLIC SCHOOLS - BUILDING AN INFRASTRUCTURE FOR PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT, 1994-1996 (Box R3241)
    - RF 94017 A 11 - UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS (EL PASO) - BUILDING AN INFRASTRUCTURE FOR PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT, 1994-1996 (Box R3241)
    - RF 94017 A 14 - NATIONAL GOVERNORS' ASSOCIATION CENTER FOR POLICY RESEARCH - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1992-1996 (Box R3241)
    - 940020-45 - SUSTAINABLE SOILS MANAGEMENT - PROGRAM OPERATIONS: SOIL MANAGEMENT OPTIONS WITH FARMERS AND EVALUATING GREEN MANURES POTENTIAL, 1994, 1997 (Box R3241)
    - 940020-52 - SIGUNGA, DALMAS- FERTILIZER NITROGEN USE EFFICIENCY AND NUTRIENT UPTAKE BY MAIZE IN A VERTISOL IN KENYA, 1994, 1997 (Box R3241)
    - RF 94020 A 56 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - BC CONFERENCE SOILS RESEARCH IN EASTERN AND SOUTHERN AFRICA, 1994-1997 (Box R3241)
    - RF 94020 A 58 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE- LAND TENURE AND AGRICULTURAL POLICY, 1994-1997 (Box R3241)
    - 1994-0021-0001 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (CIAT) - MOLECULAR MAPPING OF CASSAVA AND ITS WILD RELATIVES, 1993-1995 (Box R3241)
    - RF 94023 A 39 - CENTRO INDIGENA DE CAPACITACION INTEGRAL, A. C. (CIDECI) (MEXICO) - COMMUNITY TRAINING CENTER FOR ECO-DEVELOPMENT, 1992-1994, 1997 (Box R3241)
    - RF 94023 A 42 - INSTITUTO TECHNOLOGICO Y DE ESTUDIOS SUPERIORES DE MONTERREY (MEXICO) - SALINE AND SODIC SOILS MANAGEMENT, 1993-1997 (Box R3241)
    - RF 94024 A 84 - CHULALONGKORN UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - SOCIAL INFLUENCES ON MALE SEXUAL BEHAVIOR, 1992-1996 (Box R3241)
    - RF 94024 A 86 - THAILAND HEALTH RESEARCH INSTITUTE - THIRD INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON AIDS IN ASIA AND PACIFIC, 1994-1996 (Box R3241)
    - RF 94024 A 91 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - CONFERENCE ON A STATE-OF-THE-ART THINK TANK ON HIV VACCINES FOR DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1995 (Box R3241)
    - RF 94025 A 16 - UNIVERSITY OF ARIZONA - VIRUCIDAL FOR USE AS PROTECTION AGAINST SEXUALLY TRANSMITTED HIV, 1993-1996 (Box R3242)
    - RF 94025 A 20 - SHANGHAI INSTITUTE OF PLANNED PARENTHOOD RESEARCH (CHINA) - LEVONORGESTREL IMPLANTS/GONADAL STEROIDS, 1993-1995 (Box R3242)
    - 940026-4 - ENERGIA GLOBAL - RESIDENTIAL DEMAND-SIDE MANAGEMENT PILOT PROGRAM IN COSTA RICA, 1994-1996 (Box R3242)
    - RF 94026 A 8 - SOLAR OCEAN ENERGY, INC. -SOLAR OCEAN ENERGY CONVERSION PROJECT, 1993-1997 (Box R3242)
    - RF 94031 A 37 - FORUM ON AGRICULTURAL RESOURCE HUSBANDRY - FIRST GRANTEES MEETING, 1994-1995, 1998 (Box R3242)